polk.edu 2012-06-18

# Privacy Policy

---  
| 

> Thank you for visiting Polk State College. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit Polk State College's website, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.
> 
> When you visit the PSC website, the Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.
> 
> In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. In addition, we collect aggregate information about web browser software versions and technical capabilities such as screen resolution. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved. This information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and your personal information is not identified.
> 
> If you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to an e-newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will only be used for the purposes you authorized. Some of this information may be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the state of Florida's archiving policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by state or federal law. If information is required by law to be disclosed about you, then every effort to notify you about the disclosure in advance will be taken. If you have other questions about Polk State College privacy policies, or have suggestions on how these policies can be improved, please feel free to e-mail us at [webmaster@polk.edu](mailto:webmaster@polk.edu) or contact us by telephone at (863.297.1000). 
> 
> **Email Policy  
> **  
>  Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public record.  if you do not want your e-mail address in response to a public records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity.  Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.
> 
>  **Use and Release of Social Security Numbers**
> 
> This notice is intended for students, employees, volunteers, contractors and applicants and is made in compliance with FL Statute 119.071(5).   Polk State College (PSC) collects your SSN for use in performance of the College's duties and responsibilities for the following purposes:  classification of accounts; identification and scholarship reporting; financial aid processing; athletics recruiting; accreditation of programs; and reporting to a receiving agency or governmental entity where the disclosure is necessary to perform its duties and responsibilities.  Social security numbers are also used as a unique numeric identifier in certain cases and may be used for search purposes.  Federal Law requires that we protect social security numbers from disclosure to unauthorized parties.  Students and employees are assigned PSC identification numbers to assist in protecting their identities.
> 
> The chart listing the college areas that collect social security numbers and the laws that mandate or authorize their collection are in the SSN Collection Details pdf.  
  
Privacy | Sitemap | Contact Us | Disclaimer | [Get ADOBE READER](http://get.adobe.com/reader/)     Polk State College at 999 Avenue H NE, Winter Haven, Florida 33881, Phone 863-297-1000    
©2010 Polk State College. All rights reserved. Equal Access/Equal Opportunity Employer.
